<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Moba Projects</title>
    <link>https://expire163.github.io/moba/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Moba Projects</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 19:38:31 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://expire163.github.io/moba/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Small Engine Shed</title>
      <link>https://expire163.github.io/moba/projects/engine-shed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 19:38:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://expire163.github.io/moba/projects/engine-shed/</guid>
      <description>After some playing around with a pringles pipe as a shed i decided to upgrade to a 3d printed one.
Research Ok, calling it a research might be total overkill, but I googled for some pictures and found some nice modern sheds as a baseline.
Design Started with some flat walls that soon got upgraded corrugated iron look and some windows adding a flat roof that got extended by some roof openings printed the parts and noticed putting them together is hard if you don&amp;rsquo;t have a base to put them on created a base with some guidelines for the walls cared out of it added some doors (with just some tape acting as a hinge and spring at the same time) placed a locomotive on a track and drove in : party ;) Get some details Added a walkway to place later on some figures inside designed some window frames and glued some transparent plastic waste behind it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diy Central Station</title>
      <link>https://expire163.github.io/moba/projects/diy-central-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 09:38:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://expire163.github.io/moba/projects/diy-central-station/</guid>
      <description>Why another page about model railroads? When it comes to model railroads, you soon stumble over lots of new terms you have most likely never heard before. And when you start googeling for them you either get answers with more terms you don&amp;rsquo;t understand or a product that is quite expense.
What you find here (hopefully) I was starting out with a starter kit from Märklin and soon noticed - i want to control stuff not only by hand or the Mobile Station 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start</title>
      <link>https://expire163.github.io/moba/projects/start/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 10:19:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://expire163.github.io/moba/projects/start/</guid>
      <description>To know or not to know &amp;hellip; As i&amp;rsquo;m looking quite often in new (tech) topics, i would like to share some of my learnings with you and also persist the stuff i learned a little bit.
What to find here Most likely not too much - as documentation is not always the first thinks people like todo ;)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
